<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-03-30T23:27:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>This cool thing: Instastock</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/this-cool-thing-instastock/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/this-cool-thing-instastock/</id>
    <published>2015-03-30T23:27:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-03-30T23:54:39-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sometimes staring blankly into the void of the internet produces interesting results. It's like fishing. There are days when you sit contemplatively looking out on the placid waters (drunk), and there are days when you reel in something worthwhile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was the latter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.instastock.co"&gt;Instastock&lt;/a&gt; is a relatively new project from &lt;a href="http://www.dylansimel.com/"&gt;Dylan Simel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He joins the growing number of people and sites giving royalty free stock photos away for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.unsplash.com"&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt; and other sites have been invaluable to me in my day job, where I try to make a lot of online courses less ugly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dylan's work though interests me on a number of levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Firstly there is the discipline of adding an image a day&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The glimpses of North Carolina and has travels offer valuable and different perspectives&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is all shot with his iPhone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After learning about his site, I immediately sat up from my internet fishing and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Decided that I need that discipline of doing something every day&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Realized that my unique contexts and circumstances might offer valuable and different perspectives&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Remembered that I hate taking pictures with my Galaxy S4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for that &lt;a href="http://www.dylansimel.com/"&gt;Dylan Simel&lt;/a&gt;… thanks&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>This Damn Bag</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/this-damn-bag/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/this-damn-bag/</id>
    <published>2015-03-29T03:20:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-03-29T14:22:41-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="This Bag Torment/Relieves Me" src="/images/bag.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Walgreen's plastic bag entered our lives during a particularly windy day last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It greets me every day. Sometimes waving. Sometimes more lethargic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has caused brainstorming sessions about possible ways to remove it. It has made me want to buy one of those expensive ladders from Costco. It has survived being pelted by rocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife thinks it mocks us. I think it gives us a gentle reminder about our place in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its humble indifference is a testament to the importance of acceptance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a guerilla sculpture about the excesses of capitalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a challenge without a particularly compelling need for a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a constant reminder of how nice it would be to have that expensive Costco ladder. I mean really for only a couple hundred bucks I could snag that bag and also dust those high up walls in our apartment. 30 minutes of manual labor bliss is a bargain at half the price.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>When am I supposed to feel like an adult?</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/impending-adulthood/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/impending-adulthood/</id>
    <published>2015-03-27T20:36:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-03-29T21:14:02-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A week after a wonderful wedding reception, secluded in a tiny Colorado town for a miniature honeymoon, I asked my new wife an important question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When are we supposed to feel like adults?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It hadn't happened yet.  I thought the wedding might do it.  There were vows, pictures, delicious cakes, and smiling faces.  None of that resulted in a feeling of adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I certainly feel like I know "How to Adult". That training began early. I am an only child. I never understood that I was a kid because there weren't other models of identity available.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While I think that I do a passable job of impersonating an adult when people are watching, I definitely have impostor syndrome.  I'm not afraid that someone will find out that I'm not an actual adult. That would be a relief. Adulting is a lot of work.  It is exhausting. I'm glad that I don't have to do it all the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife's response was…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I think when we have kids&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This makes sense.  Babies are clearly not adults.  When changing one's diaper, it is also very clear that one is not a baby.  That would sort of make us feel like an adult by default.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think we'll feel like adults when none of the other options makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
