<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Blog Name</title>
  <subtitle>Blog subtitle</subtitle>
  <id>http://blog.url.com/</id>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/"/>
  <link href="http://blog.url.com/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
  <updated>2015-04-08T20:17:00-06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Blog Author</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>Creativity and Narcissism</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/creativity-and-narcissism/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/creativity-and-narcissism/</id>
    <published>2015-04-08T20:17:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-04-09T22:00:08-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Where I grew up, being of service is the primary measure of value.  This sentiment works for both people and things.  A pristine gold encrusted shovel locked behind glass is not valuable.  A genius spinster writing her days away only gains value once her work is published.  Industry for its own sake is vanity. These are the rules laid out by a radical, and possibly militant, pragmatism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most productive creative people I know are driven primarily by personal passion. Some are escaping demons, others seem to produce almost by reflex. That powerful passion though is the most pervasive throughline in my admittedly somewhat limited sample set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These beautiful, creative minds do their work because it is important to them.  That internal engine leads them to do great things if only to scratch that itch of theirs.  It effortlessly fuels late night hours or manic sprints and bursts of creativity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mine sputters.  At every step along the way the dampers of "so what" choke off the oxygen.  I have literally worked for free sweeping out trailers while working for a man who would email us about that football team in Denver he owned. There was no question in my mind in picking up that broom, but I sometimes have to build myself up to sitting down in a comfy chair with a laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What gives? That makes zero sense to me and yet it is often my reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There must be a better way. Some sort of Nash equilibrium where the optimal path is service to oneself and to others.  I stumble across it sometimes but couldn't point it out to you on a map.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Consumption vs Creation</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/consumption-vs-creation/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/consumption-vs-creation/</id>
    <published>2015-04-08T20:01:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-04-08T20:15:58-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Consumption is very easy.  We start as infants.  Capitalism wouldn't be quite so appealing if it were hard to get people to buy things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You would think, that in order for there to be some balance, the creation of things would be a comparable process.  How else would we find some much to consume if it wasn't also being created?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this all just a side effect of the Industrial Age?  Did we use to be a world of creators and consumers in equal measure?  Did the steam engine tilt the scales so far in the direction of creation that it perversely made it harder to create things?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I sometimes find myself staring at media that I have no interest in.  Last night I spent an hour listening to Friends with my eyes closed.  Surely a few minutes of typing would be easier than that particular endurance test.  Listening to the holiday armadillo for the umpteenth time can not be an easier task than writing this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And yet….&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Under the hood: Middleman is like Methadone</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/under-the-hood-middleman-is-like-methadone/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/under-the-hood-middleman-is-like-methadone/</id>
    <published>2015-04-01T22:31:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-04-01T23:29:03-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am fascinated by content management systems. I have toyed around with: Wordpress, Movable Type, Drupal, Cascade, and others that I've forgotten. For work, I get to hack on Blackboard Learn and Moodle nearly every day. Years ago I even got to work on a cutting edge experimental scholarly digital publishing platform called &lt;a href="http://scalar.usc.edu"&gt;Scalar&lt;/a&gt;.  By "work on" I mean beta test and pitch a few wireframes to some very patient developers who then smiled, nodded, and patted me on the head. Check it out, the product is much better off without my suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I've even tried my hand at writing a few of my own.  My efforts generally came to an end once my hack job zombie creation proved that it could shuffle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Writing your own blogging engine is a good early programming task.  It is very easy to be excited by it at the beginning.  They are easy to understand and produce a couple of interesting wrinkles to code around.  This practice has the romantic appeal of a carpenter making his own tools.  It has a seductive allure. It is a lumbersexual-Protestant-work-ethic-pulling-yourself-up-by-your-bootstraps wrapper for staring at your belly button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Staring at your belly button is fantastic. My mother confirms that I used to spend hours folded up investigating mine.  At the right age, this narcissism is adorable and probably an important Freudian stage of development.  I still think it is a great learning-to-program project, but it also probably needs to stop at some point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have spent countless hours fiddling with tools to amplify my voice, when I would have been better off working on things for that voice to say.  At some point, preparation becomes procrastination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spent the better part of a week trying to figure out the perfect platform on which to run this site.  I even considered diving into the world of graph databases just to stay current.  In the end, I realized that what I wanted was to write every day.  The writing was the focus on this particular project. Learning a new technology was not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I drew some inspiration from this &lt;a href="http://www.sitepoint.com/free-static-sites-middleman-github/"&gt;Sitepoint article&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href="http://benjamintan.io/"&gt;Benjamin Tan&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href="https://middlemanapp.com/"&gt;Middleman&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://middlemanapp.com/"&gt;Middleman&lt;/a&gt; has been a great way to start quickly and doesn't feel completely prepackaged either. I hope it breaks my cycle of technology-for-its-own-sake addiction by gently scratching my New Englander itch to build a site out of a tree I felled with my bare hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://middlemanapp.com/"&gt;Middleman&lt;/a&gt; is like Methadone. (They did not use this tagline)&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>On Getting Married (part 1)</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/on-getting-married/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/on-getting-married/</id>
    <published>2015-03-31T22:25:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-04-01T20:54:04-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I never thought much about getting married when I was younger.  I had decided that I was pro-marriage, but that was as far as that thought process went. I never fantasized about my wedding (which ended up being awesome). I never cut out clips of magazines or prayed for the day when my wife would arrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Marriage was, for lack of a better term, transparent. I definitely imagined fatherhood, but in those moments the wife was always conveniently out of frame.  When I imagined childbirth, it always carried the cliche moment of her hand squeezing the life out of mine. Her face, though, was always obscured, like a neighbor in a Tim Allen sitcom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This never bothered me. I never tried to reverse engineer it from the images of my dream children's faces.  I was never curious, which is weird for me.  That's the power of transparency. It is the naturalization of obfuscation. It is so powerful that it erases the very notion of focusing on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife is no longer transparent. I can see her face now. It's gently squished into the pillow and lit by the spill of my laptop screen. Her face has been remastered in all my dream reruns. Now I only have difficulty imagining it not being there.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>This cool thing: Instastock</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/this-cool-thing-instastock/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/this-cool-thing-instastock/</id>
    <published>2015-03-30T03:27:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-03-31T22:15:37-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Sometimes staring blankly into the void of the internet produces interesting results. It's like fishing. There are days when you sit contemplatively looking out on the placid waters (drunk), and there are days when you reel in something worthwhile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today was the latter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.instastock.co"&gt;Instastock&lt;/a&gt; is a relatively new project from &lt;a href="http://www.dylansimel.com/"&gt;Dylan Simel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He joins the growing number of people and sites giving royalty free stock photos away… for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.unsplash.com"&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt; and other sites have been invaluable to me in my day job, where I try to make a lot of online courses less ugly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dylan's work though interests me on a number of levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;I admire his discipline of adding an image a day.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The glimpses of North Carolina and his travels offer valuable and different perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It is all shot with his iPhone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After learning about his site, I immediately sat up from my internet fishing and&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;decided that I need that discipline of doing something every day&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;realized that my unique contexts and circumstances might offer valuable and different perspectives&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;remembered that I hate taking pictures with my Galaxy S4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for that &lt;a href="http://www.dylansimel.com/"&gt;Dylan Simel&lt;/a&gt;… thanks&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>This Damn Bag</title>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://blog.url.com/posts/this-damn-bag/"/>
    <id>http://blog.url.com/posts/this-damn-bag/</id>
    <published>2015-03-29T03:20:00-06:00</published>
    <updated>2015-03-29T14:22:41-06:00</updated>
    <author>
      <name>Article Author</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="This Bag Torment/Relieves Me" src="/images/bag.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Walgreen's plastic bag entered our lives during a particularly windy day last year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It greets me every day. Sometimes waving. Sometimes more lethargic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has caused brainstorming sessions about possible ways to remove it. It has made me want to buy one of those expensive ladders from Costco. It has survived being pelted by rocks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My wife thinks it mocks us. I think it gives us a gentle reminder about our place in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Its humble indifference is a testament to the importance of acceptance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a guerilla sculpture about the excesses of capitalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a challenge without a particularly compelling need for a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a constant reminder of how nice it would be to have that expensive Costco ladder. I mean really for only a couple hundred bucks I could snag that bag and also dust those high up walls in our apartment. 30 minutes of manual labor bliss is a bargain at half the price.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>
